5kplayer.com 2018-10-22

# Privacy Policy - DearMob

_DearMob products and services target at oversea markets outside of mainland China. For users from mainland China, please find our authorized agencies in your region to buy DearMob products._

Your privacy is important to DearMob. We recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personal information you share with us. To assist you, we provide this Privacy Statement explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information may be collected and used.

We guaranty any of your information collected from DearMob will be handled very carefully as written below. DearMob encourages you to read this privacy policy and those of all websites you visit and now please take a moment to read the following to learn more about our information practices, including what type of information is gathered, how the information is used and for what purposes, to whom we disclose the information, and how we safeguard your personal information.

#### Why we collect personal information

Your information will help us to deliver a superior customer service. It enables us to give you convenient access to our products. Your personal information helps us keep you posted on the latest product announcements, software updates, and events that you might like to hear about. Also, the user activity on website helps us to gain insights about how to improve the functionality and user experience of the website for analytics purpose. 

### What information we collect and how we collect 

General Statistical Information, Personal Identifying Information, and some data relating to the use of our software, we are providing you with this policy to inform you of how we use and, in limited circumstances, disclose such information.   
**General statistical information** includes, but is not limited to, number of hits on our websites, device platform/geo percentages of visits to website, frequency of download, installation, uninstallation, and checking for update, best software solution recommendations (5KPlayer side window), etc. through **Google Analytics**.   
**Your personal information** , include but is not limited to your first name, last name, country, email address (5KPlayer registration needs above four types of information), state, city, zip code, billing type ( _ _Your credit card number and valid date are not visible to us!__ ), currency, order number & order status on our product purchase platform 2Checkout.   
**Some software usage related data** , DOES NOT mean the video, music, DVD, radio you played, downloaded or streamed nor any file you transferred, password for file encryption with DearMob mobile management tool, we don't collect any of these information. We will only recommend you to copy the Log File to send us when you have any issue during the usage of the product. Take DearMob iPhone Manager as example, the Log file records user's previous operation, encoutered errors, device type, software version, and iOS version. You can find it on DearMob iPhone Manager software "About" > "Sent Feedback", then a window will pop up, there contains the Log File. _We can only view the information when you send it to us._ By sending the Log File to us, you agree to share it with DearMob. We will use such information to investigate the issue you encounter in order to provide individual assistance. We promise that we will never publish or share any of your Log File outside DearMob.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes a unique identifier that is sent to your computer or mobile phone browser from a website's computer and is stored on your device's hard drive. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser's preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites. Cookies record information about your online preferences and allow us to tailor the websites to your interests.

**Website Cookie:** We use third-party Google Analytis to monitor web traffic, statistics, advertisement 'click-through', and other activities on DearMob's site. Where authorized by us, such third parties may use cookies, our web log files, web beacons, and other monitoring technologies to evaluate use of our website. 

**Shopping Cart Based on Geo:** You will enter the shopping cart secured by 2Checkout when you click the buy button on our website. Here 2Checkout uses technology to identify your geo in order to deliver shopping cart in the correct language and local currency in the event of a purchase.

**Embed URL:** DearMob may embed URL on its official website and in program to evaluate the performance of the website and program without cookies. Embedded URLs allow limited information to follow you as you navigate the electronic Channels, but are not associated with Personal Information and are not used beyond the session.

#### Placing Orders

DearMob may use Personal Information to engage in transactions with you and use Personal Information along with financial, credit card, and payment information, to process your transactions.

DearMob employs secure server hosted by 2Checkout that encrypt the customer's personal information listed below for purchase before it is sent to us, including name, email address, country, state, city, zip code, currency for purchase. Encryption works to prevent any malicious use of your personal information.

Founded in 2006, 2Checkout has the US headquarters in Atlanta and the European headquarters in Amsterdam, The Netherlands. 2Checkout is an advanced secure online payment service for software registration. DearMob uses 2Checkout to provide you with very secure and fast online purchase.

#### Contest and Giveaways

Besides the paid software registration, DearMob also constantly holds software free giveaways or contests to win a gift. We may ask you to provide your email address in order to send you the software registration code and keep the file to draw the winner of a contest. But you also have the right to ask us to delete your email from our system.

_We may subsequently send software guides, update notification or related deals via the email address you submitted. We use trusted third-party email services to send such kind of messages or newsletters. You can change your subscription preference or opt-out at any time._

#### Contact Us & Tech Support

We may collect or ask you to provide necessary information when you reach us by email, by business cooperation, signing up our Affiliate Program, or by requesting technical support which includes, but not limited to, the emails are sending to media@5kplayer.com, business@5klayer.com, contact@5kpayer.com, sales@5kplayer.com, affiliate@5kplayer.com and support@5kplayer.com.

This information may include, without limitation, your licensed email address, order ID, what features you use in our software, how you use our software, your computer or device information, log file, and sometines the media files you want to process with our softwre, etc. In general, we collect no more information than is required in order to investigate the issue you encounter. 

This information is collected to help us to provide services and support, to help us solve the technology problems you are experiencing. By sending the related information to us, you agree to share them with DearMob. If you do not want to share the information with DearMob, don't included in the email. We will use any such information only when providing individual support or assistance, and will not retain such information any longer than necessary for this purpose. We promise that we will never publish or share any of your information outside DearMob. And the media files you give to us will never be disclosed outside DearMob. We may retain the media files anonymously and confidentially for internal R&D to improve the product performance.

#### None Personal Information

We may collect some none personal information which aims to validate your registration and to know how you use our software or services. The information may include operating system, device ID, Internet protocol addresses, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages, clickstream data of our websites and our products or services, and the pages or features of our software or services accessed by you and the time spent there. 

### How We Use Your Information

Product Registration, Online Support and Product Warranty.

Answer to inquiries： Improve Products, Services, and Experiences.

Post Testimonials：We display name, testimonials and pictures of satisfied customers on our websites with their consent. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, please [contact us](mailto:support@5kplayer.com) with your request. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

E-mail Newsletters：We will send you product update or services information, marketing... 

Other purposes upon prior notice and approval.

### How We Share Your Information

DearMob keeps your personal information confidential. We will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Unless we have your permission, we will not use or share your personal information in ways unrelated to the ones described at the time you provide the data. Only with one exception as below: 

**Government and Law Enforcement** We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on DearMob; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of DearMob(including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of DearMob services or members of the public. 

### Your Choices

You may choose whether or not to provide personal information to DearMob or you can unsubscribe from any tailor-made promotional email from our company. If you want to delete your account, your personal information that is stored in our databases or want to opt-out of our services, please contact our [Customer Support](mailto:support@5kplayer.com). The notice we provide to you whenever DearMob collects your personal information will explain the purpose of which the data is being collected and should help you make this choice.

DearMob offers you the opportunity to choose whether your personal information is (a) to be disclosed to a non-agent third party or (b) to be used for a purpose other than the purpose for which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized by you. DearMob will provide you reasonable mechanisms to exercise your choices at the data collection point or by using other methods.

### Children's Privacy

DearMob does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 16 and its websites do not target children under 16. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children's online activities and interests.

### Keeping Your Personal Information Secure

DearMob takes seriously the trust you place in us. To protect against unauthorized access, misuse, disclosure, or alteration of your personal information, DearMob employs appropriate physical, technical, and administrative measures. These measures include: 

Physical security is designed to prevent unauthorized access to database equipment and hard copies of documents. When we transmit highly confidential information over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layers (SSL) protocol.

Electronic security measures, such as firewalls, access restrictions, and encryption provide protection from hacking or other unauthorized access. DearMob limits access to personal information to those persons in DearMob’s organization, or as agents of DearMob, who have a specific business purpose for maintaining and processing personal information and data.

No one can guarantee, and we do not guarantee, that your personal information is completely secure at all times. You are also responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your personal information to protect it against unauthorized access or use. If a password is used to help protect your accounts and personal information, it is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer or device with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving a site or service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. 

DearMob is concerned about controlling unsolicited commercial email, or "spam". DearMob has a strict Anti-Spam Policy restricting the use of customer account to send commercials. DearMob will not sell, lease or rent its email subscriber lists to third parties. Any unsubscribed emails will be immediately take out from our list.

### How to Change or Delete Your Personal Information

If you want us to correct, amend, or delete your personal information, newsletter subscriptions, or your support tickets, please [contact us](mailto:support@5kplayer.com) with your request. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe. However, some information may remain in archived/backup copies to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

For the information processed by the third party partners, you have the right to access your personal information. If you want to access, correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data on our third party partner's platform, you should contact them directly as they are the data controllers and DearMob has no control of those information.

### Changes to This Privacy Policy

All updates to this policy will be posted here. Last update: May 24, 2018. We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes in our services and customer feedback. We encourage you to periodically review this Privacy Policy to be informed of how DearMob is protecting your information.

### Contact Information

DearMob regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or DearMob's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this website. If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or believe that DearMob has not adhered to this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](mailto:support@5klpayer.com) and we will make efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem.
